overstockstrading.com 2014-05-06

# ..::Over Stocks Trading::..

**Information You Give Us**

We receive and may store any information you enter on our website or give to our website in any other way. For example, we collect information you provide when you place an order, register with us, send us an e-mail or call us, enter a sweepstakes, or enroll or participate in a club or service such as gift registries. This information may include:

• Your name.  
• Your mailing address.  
• Your e-mail address.  
• Your phone number.  
• The first and last four digits of your credit card number.

It may also include any other personal or preference information you provide to us or information you submit about other people, for example, the name and address of a gift recipient. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email. This practice, called "phishing", is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, DO NOT RESPOND

**Automatic Information**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, we use "cookies" like many other websites. Through "cookies" we obtain information when your web browser accesses ours. There are utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously. We cannot provide you with a personalized experience or certain services at our website if we cannot recognize you, therefore, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

**Protection of Our Website and Others**

We may disclose information you provide to our website when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our website, our users or others.

**What about links to and from other websites?**

Our website may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. In addition, you may have linked to our website through another site. For example, in certain cases you may have linked to Overstocks Trading through banner advertising on another site. In such cases the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites as well to see how they collect and use data

**Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this online privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy so we encourage you to review it periodically.

**Warning about Fraudulent Emails**

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

**Sharing with Other Companies**

Overstocks Trading does not rent or sell your information to outside marketers. Overstocks Trading may share your information with members of the Overstocks Trading family of businesses to provide you with products or services that you have requested or to provide you with promotional offers that Overstocks Trading believes are of interest to you. In certain circumstances, Overstocks Trading may share your information with service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services for Overstocks Trading. To ensure the confidentiality and security of your information, service providers must agree to safeguard your information in strict compliance with this policy. Overstocks Trading may also provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe, in good faith, that the law requires it. There may be instances when Overstocks Trading may access or disclose your information to protect or defend the legal rights or property of Overstocks Trading and its affiliated companies or their employees and agents, to protect the safety and security of users and members of Overstocks Trading, and to protect against fraud.
